Guide to the Clark E. Warburton papers, 1920-1979
George Mason University Libraries
- Clark Warburton Papers
  - Theory of Monetary Disequilibrium- Chapters 5-9 (Working copy) (1) (Folder 24, Box 16)
  - Theory of Monetary Disequilibrium- Chapters 5-9 (Working copy) (2) (Folder 25, Box 16)
  - The Role of Money in Business Fluctuations- manuscript (Folder 26, Box 16)
  - Articles included in Depression, Inflation and Monetary Policy (Folder 1, Box 17)
  - Articles in Depression, Inflation and Monetary Theory- CW copy while in process (1) (Folder 2, Box 17)
  - Articles in Depression, Inflation and Monetary Theory- CW copy while in process (2) (Folder 3, Box 17)
  - Articles in Depression, Inflation and Monetary Theory- CW copy while in process (3) (Folder 4, Box 17)
  - Banking and Business Fluctuations- Erratic Money (First draft) (Folder 5, Box 17)
  - Business Fluctuations- Historical Reprints (Includes application of Betly A.M. Ratz) (Folder 6, Box 17)
  - Contents- Depression, Inflation and Monetary Policy- A collection of articles (Folder 7, Box 17)
  - Chapters 1-8 - Depression, Inflation and Monetary Policy- A collection of articles (1) (Folder 8, Box 17)
  - Chapters 1-8 - Depression, Inflation and Monetary Policy- A collection of articles (2) (Folder 9, Box 17)
  - Depression, Inflation and Monetary Policy- Part two, Chapters 9-15 (Folder 10, Box 17)
  - Depression, Inflation and Monetary Policy- Part Three and Four, Chapters 16-28 (Folder 11, Box 17)
  - Depression, Inflation and Monetary Policy- Part Five, Chapters 29-35 (Folder 12, Box 17)
  - Depression, Inflation and Monetary Theory- extra contents, preface, introduction (Folder 13, Box 17)
  - Material regarding research in relation of banking to business fluctuations (Folder 14, Box 17)
  - Notes on this group of obsolete manuscripts (Folder 15, Box 17)
  - "Nonmembers banks and effectiveness of monetary policy" in Monetary Management (Prentice Hall, 1963) pp.317-359 (1) (Folder 16, Box 17)
  - "Nonmember banks and the effectiveness of monetary policy"- tables and copies to be used for xeroxing (2) (Folder 17, Box 17)
  - "Nonmember banks and the effectiveness of monetary policy"- tables and copies to be used for xeroxing (3) (Folder 18, Box 17)
  - "Nonmember banks and the effectiveness of the monetary policy"- rough draft (4) (Folder 19, Box 17)
  - November 11, 1966- Cyclical Fluctuations in the Stock of Money and in Effective Demand 1919-65 (Folder 20, Box 17)
  - Pamphlets History of FDIC and Prior Proposals (Folder 20A, Box 17)
  - Outlines of project regarding banking and business fluctuations, 1790-1919 (Folder 21, Box 17)
  - Plateaus of Prosperity and Plains of Depression from Economic Essays in honor of Wesley Clair Mitchell, 1935 (Folder 22, Box 17)
  - Publishers and Journals regarding quotations and reporting of articles in Mismanaged Money- Correspondence on releases of reports (Folder 23, Box 17)
  - Reply to questions regarding H.R.11 in Compendium on Monetary Policy Guidelines and Federal Reserve Structure (Folder 24, Box 17)
  - Theories of Monetary Control and Authority (Folder 25, Box 17)
  - The Great Depression- Chapter 15 (Folder 26, Box 17)
  - Assets and Liabilities of the Entire Banking and Currency System, June-December 1946-68. Factors in Growth of Deposits and Assets. (Folder 1, Box 18)
  - Charts and quarterly data from Dan Edwards regarding GNP, money supply, and other variables. (Folder 2, Box 18)
  - Contents and Chapter Outlines (Folder 3, Box 18)
  - Cyclical variations in money, etc. Rate of use for final product expenditures, 1918-63 (Measured by percentage change from same quarter of preceding year). (Folder 4, Box 18)
  - Data for member bank reserves and deposits subject to reserve, 1960-1917-1929. (Folder 5, Box 18)
  - Data for final product expenditures by business and individuals. 1919-63 (Folder 6, Box 18)
  - Data for F.R. last Wednesday in month series (Deposit adjusted and currency outside banks- money held by business and individuals) 1946-63 (Folder 7, Box 18)
  - Data pertaining to money held by business and individuals. 1909-46 (Folder 8, Box 18)
  - Deposits adjusted and currency outside banks. 1918-64 (Folder 9, Box 18)
  - Deposits adjusted and currency outside banks- excluding and including time and savings(Mid year and end year). (Folder 10, Box 18)
  - Deposits of State and Local Government 1919-64 (Folder 11, Box 18)
  - Estimated Gross National Product from Kendrick Productivity Trends in U.S. 1919-47 (Folder 12, Box 18)
  - Estimates of foreign deposits in IPC accounts. 1918-1964 (Folder 13, Box 18)
  - Federal Reserves Money Supply- 1964 series (Folder 14, Box 18)
  - Final product expenditures by business and individuals. 1964-70 (Folder 15, Box 18)
  - Flow of Funds- Quarterly Table 11-23-1965 (Folder 16, Box 18)
  - Indexes of effective member banks reserves 1918-63 (Folder 17, Box 18)
  - Indexes of money held by business and individuals based on F.R. 1946-63 (Folder 18, Box 18)
  - Indexes of rate of use of money for final product expenditures by business and individuals. 1946-63 (Folder 19, Box 18)
  - Indexes of money held by business and individuals. 1918-60 (Folder 20, Box 18)
  - Indexes of Gross National Product- Current dollars and constant dollars. 1919-64 (Folder 21, Box 18)
  - Indexes of final product expenditures by business and individuals. 1919-63 (Folder 22, Box 18)
  - Indexes: Money supply, GNP, etc. 1918-61, 1918-63 (Folder 23, Box 18)
  - Lists and descriptions of tables (Folder 24, Box 18)
  - Losses in Operations- Closed banks 1865-1940 (Folder 25, Box 18)
  - Materials for price index and money holdings of individuals. (Folder 26, Box 18)
  - Member bank reserves and deposits subject to reserves- 1929-64 monthly data. (Folder 27, Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous notes and materials to be filed. (Folder 28, Box 18)
  - National income and product accounts 1967-71 (Folder 29, Box 18)
  - Price indexes, 1919-47 and components of GNP. (Folder 30, Box 18)
  - Price Indexes (Folder 31, Box 18)
  - Quarterly trend of values at various rates and dates. (Folder 32, Box 18)
  - Relation of GNP to money stock 1919-64 (Folder 33, Box 18)
  - Rotating of Federal Reserves operations to business fluctuations. (Folder 34, Box 18)
  - Seasonally adjusted quarterly indexes of money held by business and individuals in series. 1918-47 (Folder 35, Box 18)
  - Seasonally adjusted quarterly indexes of stock of money. 1918-60 (Folder 36, Box 18)
  - Seasonally adjusted quarterly indexes of stock of money in series. (Folder 37, Box 18)
  - FR Study I " Postwar Relationships Between GNP and Alternatively Defined Money Supplies" and FR Monthly Statistics- Selected Liquid Assets held by Public. (Folder 38, Box 18)
  - Tables From Index Members of the Equation of Exchange and Seasonally Adjusted Index of Money Held by Business and Individuals, 1918-50. (Folder 39, Box 18)
  - Tax and government data for estimates of final expenditure by business and individuals, 1919-63 and GNP 1919-38. (Folder 40, Box 18)
  - Text with carbons- Chapter I. (Folder 41, Box 18)
  - Text and original tables- Chapter II. (Folder 42, Box 18)
  - Text- Chapter III. (Folder 43, Box 18)
  - Text- Chapter IV. (Folder 44, Box 18)
  - Text- Chapter V. (Folder 45, Box 18)
  - Text- Chapter VI.- Technical Framework and Methology. (Folder 46, Box 18)
  - Text- Chapter VII. (Folder 47, Box 18)
  - Text- Chapter VIII. (Folder 48, Box 18)
  - Text with two carbons- Chapter IX. (Tables only) (Folder 49, Box 18)
  - Data for monthly estimates- Total deposits adjusted and currency outside banks. 1919-64 (Folder 50, Box 18)
  - Alabama- Banking history (Folder 1, Box 19)
  - Assets and liabilities of Federal Reserve banks- unpublished items. (Folder 2, Box 19)
  - First Bank of U.S. (Folder 3, Box 19)
  - Second Bank of U.S. (Folder 4, Box 19)
  - Banking Difficulties of the 1830's (Folder 5, Box 19)
  - Bank History Study (Folder 6, Box 19)
  - Bank records projects- Banks in operation prior to 1875. (Folder 7, Box 19)
  - Banks in operation prior to 1860 (Folder 8, Box 19)
  - Banks established during 1780-1820 (Folder 9, Box 19)
  - Banks established during 1800-1820 (Folder 10, Box 19)
  - Bank reserves and circulation medium- National Banks 1865-1919 (Folder 11, Box 19)
  - Check list of financial instock by states 1896-1934 (Folder 12, Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous notes- Revised all bank data by Clark Warburton. 1896-1950 (Folder 13, Box 19)
  - Commercial banking and trust company offices in continental United States. 1900-1940 (Folder 14, Box 19)
  - List of contents in card file on banking history prior to 1911. (Folder 15, Box 19)
  - Data regarding national banks 1868-1889 (Folder 16, Box 19)
  - Deposits plus circulation by states 1834-63 (Folder 17, Box 19)
  - Inflation and banking 1900-50 (Folder 18, Box 19)
  - Notes and banking data prior to 1870 (Folder 19, Box 19)
  - Louisiana (Folder 20a, Box 19)
  - Banking History (Folder 20b, Box 19)
  - Material regarding number of banks. 1812-1900 (Folder 21, Box 19)
  - Number of Banks 1854-1934 (Folder 22, Box 19)
  - Mississippi (Folder 23, Box 19)
  - Gold ans Silver Imports and Exports Prior to 1921 (Folder 24, Box 19)
  - Monetary and Banking Developments 1836-1860 (Folder 25, Box 19)
  - Monetary Disturbances 1834-45 (Folder 26, Box 19)
  - Monetary Volume and Instability 1834-45 (Folder 27, Box 19)
  - Monetary Factors in Business Fluctuations 1790-1950 (Folder 28, Box 19)
  - Monetary Factors in Business Fluctuations 1790-1950 (Folder 29, Box 19)
  - Monetary Factors in Business Fluctuations- Summary Tables (various drafts). 1790-1950 (Folder 30, Box 19)
  - Monetary Factors in Business Fluctuations 1790-1950 (Folder 31, Box 19)
  - Money, Prices and Business Fluctuations- First half of the 19th century. (Folder 32, Box 19)
  - N.Y.- Banking History (Folder 33, Box 19)
  - N.C.- Banking History (Folder 34, Box 19)
  - Number of banks, 1860-1933 and cash balances of individuals and business, 1864-1950 (Folder 35, Box 19)
  - Number of banks, call dates 1863-1917 (Folder 36, Box 19)
  - N.Y., Pa., VA. and Ohio- Combined data, specie, circulation and deposits. 1836-62 (Folder 37, Box 19)
  - Number of banks other than national. 1860-96 (Folder 38, Box 19)
  - Sources of data for relation of banking and business fluctuations 1790-1917 (Folder 39, Box 19)
  - Number of banks by years and states 1860-1900 (Folder 40, Box 19)
  - Number of banks (Folder 41, Box 19)
  - N.Y.- Call date data 1830-66 (Folder 42, Box 19)
  - Ohio- Banking history (Folder 43, Box 19)
  - Prior to 1865- Bank Suspensions (Folder 44, Box 19)
  - Postal Saving System 1911-1959 (Folder 45, Box 19)
  - Penn- Banking history (Folder 46, Box 19)
  - Pennsylvania banking statistics- Call dates 1829-1863 (Folder 47, Box 19)
  - Relation of number of banks, banking offices and deposits to population, by years 1900-36 (Folder 48, Box 19)
  - State operated controlled banks (Folder 48, Box 19)
  - Statements of assets and liabilities of the banks of the U.S. 1792-1800 (Folder 50, Box 19)
  - Selections from manuscripts on bank suspensions- History of deposit insurance and relations of banking to business fluctuations. 9-3-1953 (Folder 51, Box 19)
  - Specie holdings- European central banks. (Folder 52, Box 19)
  - S.C.- Banking history (Folder 53, Box 19)
  - The 1937-38 depression (Folder 54, Box 19)
  - U.S. Congress Documents on Banking 1836-41 (Folder 55, Box 19)
  - Virginia- Banking history (Folder 56, Box 19)
  - Virginia- Bank Capital 1835-40 (Folder 57, Box 19)
  - Work sheets on banking. (Folder 58, Box 19)
  - Appendix Tables I. Statistical Methodology- Family Income (Folder 1, Box 20)
  - Charts- Family Income (Folder 3, Box 20)
  - Charts- Family Income (Folder 4, Box 20)
  - Charts- Utilization of income by unattached individuals (Folder 5, Box 20)
  - Chart- Utilization by chief economic classes ( Family income). (Folder 6, Box 20)
  - Charts- Surveys on family expenditures. (Folder 7, Box 20)
  - Central Bank Operations and Business Fluctuations, 1919-1964- Chapters I-V. (Folder 8, Box 20)
  - Central Bank Operations and Business Fluctuations- Chapters I-IV(Finished copy). (Folder 9, Box 20)
  - Central Bank Operations and Business Fluctuations- Chapters V-IX(Finished copy). (Folder 10, Box 20)
  - Central Bank Operations and Business Fluctuations- Tables and Charts (1) (Folder 11, Box 20)
  - Central Bank Operations and Business Fluctuations- Tables and Charts (2) (Folder 12, Box 20)
  - Central Bank Operations and Business Fluctuations- Chapters VI-IX. (Folder 13, Box 20)
  - Chapter VII Expenditures for Food- Family Income (Folder 14, Box 20)
  - Chapter VIII Expenditures for Home Maintenance- Family Income (Folder 15, Box 20)
  - Chapters IX-X Other Living (Folder 16, Box 20)
  - Chapter XI Savings- Family Income (Folder 17, Box 20)
  - Chapter XIII Interrelationships among the major groups of family expenditures- Family Income. (Folder 18, Box 20)
  - Cumulative Income Distribution-Family Income (Folder 19, Box 20)
  - Data for Charts and Supporting Tables- Chapters I-VI- Family Income (Folder 20, Box 20)
  - Footnotes and worksheets of old 1965 revised annual estimates of GNP. (Folder 21, Box 20)
  - Mathematical Theory of Price, 1928 (Folder 22, Box 20)
  - Manuscript- Chapters I-VII- Family Income (Folder 23, Box 20)
  - Monetary disturbances and policies for stability (1) (Folder 24, Box 20)
  - Monetary disturbances and policies for stability (2) (Folder 25, Box 20)
  - Monetary disturbances and policies for stability (3)- Copy for printer. (Folder 26, Box 20)
  - Monetary disturbances and policies for stability (4)- Copy for printer. (Folder 27, Box 20)
  - Monetary disturbances and policies for stability (5)- Copy for printer. (Folder 28, Box 20)
  - Monetary disturbances and policies for stability (6)- Copy for printer. (Folder 29, Box 20)
  - Original tables for "Central Bank Operations and Business Fluctuations" (Folder 30, Box 20)
  - Preface- Table of contents- etc.List of budget studies and family income. (Folder 31, Box 20)
  - Price Theory, etc.-M.A. Thesis(Original) (Folder 32, Box 20)
  - Statistical Appendix- Family Income (Folder 33, Box 20)
  - The Mathematical Theory of Price- Written 1927-28 (Folder 34, Box 20)
  - The Use of Family Income- Manuscript (1) (Folder 35, Box 20)
  - The Use of Family Income- Manuscript (2) (Folder 36, Box 20)
  - A Report on Deposit Insurance by Lauchlin Currie and Martin Frost (Folder 1, Box 21)
  - Data for Bank Obligations Manuscript by Ethel Bastedo- Origin of the FDIC Law of 1933. (Folder 2, Box 21)
  - Deposit Guaranty in Mississippi, South Dakota, North Dakota, and Washington (Folder 3, Box 21)
  - Deposit Guaranty in Oklahoma and Kansas (Folder 4, Box 21)
  - Deposit Guaranty in Texas and Nebraska (Folder 5, Box 21)
  - Guaranty of Bank Obligations in the U.S., 1825-35(Preliminary draft, 1935). (Folder 6, Box 21)
  - Insurance of bank obligations in six states 1829-46(Preliminary draft of report) (Folder 7, Box 21)
  - Introductory chapter, Concluding chapter, and Bibliography (Folder 8, Box 21)
  - Kansas (Folder 9, Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous on insurance of bank obligations. (Folder 10, Box 21)
  - Mississippi (Folder 11, Box 21)
  - North Dakota (Folder 12, Box 21)
  - Nebraska (Folder 13, Box 21)
  - Oklahoma (Folder 14, Box 21)
  - Prohibition of Interest on Demand Deposits (Folder 15, Box 21)
  - Portfolios of Member Banks Suspending in 1929-30 (Folder 16, Box 21)
  - Portfolios of State Banks Suspending in the Western Grain States (Folder 17, Box 21)
  - South Dakota (Folder 18, Box 21)
  - Texas (Folder 19, Box 21)
  - Washington (Folder 20, Box 21)
  - Extracts from the Correspondence of the Board of Control, State Bank of Ohio 1848-1864 (Folder 21, Box 21)
  - Available income and the national product (1) (Folder 1, Box 22)
  - Available income and the national product (2) (Folder 2, Box 22)
  - Banking and output statistics (Folder 3, Box 22)
  - Banking and output statistics (Folder 4, Box 22)
  - Banking and business fluctuations series and extensions of some tables in banking and output statistics (1) (Folder 5, Box 22)
  - Banks and business fluctuations series and extensions of some tables in banking and output statistics (2) (Folder 6, Box 22)
  - Basis for an Economic Change- Economic Classics (Folder 7, Box 22)
  - Critique of the Summary of Contemporary Economics (Folder 8, Box 22)
  - Criteria and implementation of monetary policy (Folder 9, Box 22)
  - Correspondence regarding "measuring the lag in impact of monetary policy". (Folder 10, Box 22)
  - Corporate control and organization (Folder 11, Box 22)
  - Development of central banking theory and practice in the U.S. (Folder 12, Box 22)
  - Democracy and economic evolution (Folder 13, Box 22)
  - Democratic traditions and economic change. (Folder 14, Box 22)
  - Democratic Institutions (Folder 15, Box 22)
  - Economic classes in the U.S. (Folder 16, Box 22)
  - Federal Reserve Operations and Business Fluctuations (Folder 17, Box 22)
  - Fiscal policy and the "New Economics" (Folder 18, Box 22)
  - Functions of an Economic Sector of the Cooperative League (Folder 19, Box 22)
  - Functions and organization of an effective people's lobby. (Folder 20, Box 22)
  - Housing and construction (Folder 21, Box 22)
  - Looking Toward Permanent Full Employment (Folder 22, Box 22)
  - Monetary Policy in the U.S.- 1918-42 and 1942-47. (Folder 23, Box 22)
  - Measuring the Lag in the Impact of Monetary Policy-First typing. (Folder 24, Box 22)
  - Measuring the Lag in the Impact of the Monetary Policy-Notes on papers. (Folder 25, Box 22)
  - Measuring the Lag in the Impact of Monetary Policy- Final copy. (Folder 26, Box 22)
  - Monetary velocity and the value of output. (Folder 27, Box 22)
  - Monetary and interest rate policies. (Folder 28, Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous papers proposed for economic programs. (Folder 29, Box 22)
  - Remarks of J.L. Robertson (Folder 30, Box 22)
  - The Laffer-Ranoon model after five years. (Folder 31, Box 22)
  - Origin, development and problems of deposit insurance. (Folder 32, Box 22)
  - Our Functional Society (Folder 33, Box 22)
  - Our Changing Economic System (Folder 34, Box 22)
  - Prohibition of Interest on Demand Deposits (Folder 35, Box 22)
  - Productive Capacity and the Feasible Standard of Living for the Masses. (Folder 36, Box 22)
  - Proposals for Federal action regarding Business Recovery and Alleviation of Distress. (Folder 37, Box 22)
  - Planning without dictatorship. (Folder 38, Box 22)
  - Prohibition of Interest on Demand Deposits. (Folder 39, Box 22)
  - Reserve requirements and the role of the Federal Reserve System. (Folder 40, Box 22)
  - Price Policy for Agriculture (Folder 41, Box 22)
  - Political Party Programs and Economic Classes (Folder 42, Box 22)
  - Proposed Changes in the Basic Corporation Law (Folder 43, Box 22)
  - Development of my studies on "Monetary Policy and Business Fluctuations" (Folder 44, Box 22)
  - Reserve requirements, FED membership and monetary control(March 1979). (Folder 45, Box 22)
  - Taxation (1) (Folder 46, Box 22)
  - Taxation (2) (Folder 47, Box 22)
  - The Impact of Banking (Folder 48, Box 22)
  - The Making of Price and Production Industrial Policy (Folder 49, Box 22)
  - Theories of the relation of money to business fluctuations, 1750-1930. (Folder 50, Box 22)
  - The monetary condition for economic equilibrium. (Folder 51, Box 22)
  - Unemployment compensation. (Folder 52, Box 22)
  - An emergency currency based upon warehouse receipts for a composite group of basic commodities, 1933. (Folder 1, Box 23)
  - Stabilization of Currencies by International Agreement. (Folder 2, Box 23)
  - A National Currency Authority (Folder 3, Box 23)
  - A proposal to consolidate the public debt and to protect bank deposits. (Folder 4, Box 23)
  - Accounting Methodology in Measurements of National Income. (Folder 5, Box 23)
  - Asset liquidity and monetary policy. (Folder 6, Box 23)
  - Bank suspensions and the banking and monetary structures. (Folder 7, Box 23)
  - basic commodity monetary standard. (Folder 8, Box 23)
  - Commodity monetary standard. (Folder 9, Box 23)
  - Comments on present monetary and banking system. (Folder 10, Box 23)
  - Can we manage the currency? (Folder 11, Box 23)
  - Correspondence regarding monetary and banking reform. (Folder 12, Box 23)
  - Theory of Business Fluctuations. (Folder 13, Box 23)
  - Comments of papers at American Economic Association and Conference on Research on Income and Wealth. (Folder 14, Box 23)
  - Causes of Business Fluctuations. (Folder 15, Box 23)
  - Comments on the Equation of Exchange. (Folder 16, Box 23)
  - Data- Monetary volume- Prices (Folder 17, Box 23)
  - Dual Banking (Folder 18, Box 23)
  - Economic Background of Bank Suspensions. (Folder 19, Box 23)
  - Effect of credit expansion and money supply upon the national income. (Folder 20, Box 23)
  - Effect of wartime monetary expansion on the postwar price level. (Folder 21, Box 23)
  - Fallacy and truth in explanations of the depression. (Folder 22, Box 23)
  - Forecast of gross income in the U.S. in April 1943. (Folder 23, Box 23)
  - Forecasting the pressure on prices in 1943-44-45. (Folder 24, Box 23)
  - Forecasting price inflation in 1944. (Folder 25a, Box 23)
  - Financial institutions in the District of Columbia. (Folder 25b, Box 23)
  - Government financing and the pressure on prices. (Folder 26, Box 23)
  - Income flow and monetary instability, 1909-43. (Folder 27, Box 23)
  - International monetary stabilization. (Folder 28, Box 23)
  - Memos to Mr. Thompson (Folder 29a, Box 23)
  - Government financing and pressure on prices. (Folder 29b, Box 23)
  - Monetary reform proposals prior to 1935. (Folder 30, Box 23)
  - Monetary and fiscal policies of the federal government. (Folder 31, Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous- Suggestions on banking, money, and use of money. (Folder 32, Box 23)
  - Memorandum- Changes in the banking system. (Folder 33, Box 23)
  - Banking and Business Fluctuations. (Folder 34, Box 23)
  - Mr. Hart and the Model (Folder 35, Box 23)
  - Non-Inflationary Financing of the War. (Folder 36, Box 23)
  - Program for financial research- National Bureau of Economic Research and Reserve City Banks Association. (Folder 37, Box 23)
  - Functions of Banking and Monetary Institutions. (Folder 38, Box 23)
  - Notes on Monetary Theory (Folder 39, Box 23)
  - Preparation for Post-War Banking Difficulties. (Folder 40, Box 23)
  - Post-War Currency Stabilization (Folder 41, Box 23)
  - Proposed changes in Federal government obligations to avoid further inflationary financing. (Folder 42, Box 23)
  - Prosperity and Famine in the Hauran (Folder 43, Box 23)
  - Savings and Capital Formation 1909-33 (Folder 44, Box 23)
  - Savings and Economic Instability (Folder 45, Box 23)
  - Suburban Development and the Business Situation (Folder 46, Box 23)
  - The pressure of the inflationary gap upon prices. (Folder 47, Box 23)
  - The "managed" currency and the prospects of inflation. (Folder 48, Box 23)
  - The task of the Council of Economic Advisors. (Folder 49, Box 23)
  - Volume and classification of payments in the U.S., 1929. (Folder 50, Box 23)
  - Wartime Federal Government Borrowing (Folder 51, Box 23)
  - Wartime inflation and the pressure on prices (1). (Folder 52, Box 23)
  - Wartime inflation and the pressure on prices (2). (Folder 53, Box 23)
  - Antitrust in Banking (Folder 1, Box 24)
  - Absorption of Exchange Changes (Folder 2, Box 24)
  - Central Bank Operators and Business, 1919-64. (Folder 3, Box 24)
  - Central Bank Operators and Business- Library of Congress. (Folder 4, Box 24)
  - Charts regarding money, monetized assets, reserves, etc. for 1918-48 period. (Folder 5, Box 24)
  - Charts on expenditures on final products and rate of use of money for 1919-56 period. (Folder 6, Box 24)